<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>general on Tomasz Kyc Webpage and Blog</title><link>https://tomaszkyc.github.io/tags/general/</link><description>Recent content in general on Tomasz Kyc Webpage and Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 20:49:12 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tomaszkyc.github.io/tags/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Github Actions - simple CI/CD</title><link>https://tomaszkyc.github.io/blog/github-actions-simple-cicd/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 20:49:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://tomaszkyc.github.io/blog/github-actions-simple-cicd/</guid><description>Hello fellows!
Good to see you all. It was a really busy time but it happened - finally found time to write some post about my observations related with GitHub Actions as a good CICD solution that costs almost nothing.
Why do I need CI/CD? That&amp;rsquo;s a good question though. First you need to think if:
you have some tasks like some unit / integration tests you would like to run every time you push new commit to the branch it takes you a lot of time to run all the commands and do the app release you want to verify each time your commits quality is good enough (e.</description></item><item><title>Christmas time and New Year's Eve - time for summary</title><link>https://tomaszkyc.github.io/blog/christmas-time-and-new-years-eve-time-for-summary/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 20:49:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://tomaszkyc.github.io/blog/christmas-time-and-new-years-eve-time-for-summary/</guid><description>Hello fellows. I hope you&amp;rsquo;re doing well and maybe bake some delicious christmas cakes. That was a preety long year for me. Especially when I list some events there:
Learning .NET Core and Angular Making diploma project and finishing my CS studies with 5.0 grade Developing my Java and Python skills Unexpected changing a job (which maybe I will describe in the future) But now it&amp;rsquo;s time to slow down, take a deep breath and spend some time with closest people out there.</description></item></channel></rss>